就像你对我的所作所为一样吗
You mean the same courtesy you've extended me?
你的委员会在调查总统  参议员
Your committee is investigating the President, Senator.
这根本不是一码事  白宫也没有人
It is hardly the same thing. Nobody at the White House
在为难你的妻子和孩子
is impugning your wife or your children.
我只是在跟着证据走
I'm only following the evidence where it leads.
证据  什么证据
Evidence? What evidence?
她只是个普通公民
This is a civilian we're talking about.
她根本就不在此事的调查范围内
She is so far outside the scope of the inquiry,
简直可笑
it is laughable.
我想你没有自己以为的那样了解她
I don't think you know her as well as you think you do.
这话又是什么意思
And what's that supposed to mean?
我想明天我们就知道了  不是吗
I guess we'll find out tomorrow, won't we?